You are given NN sticks, where the length of each stick is a positive integer. A cut operation is performed on the sticks such that all of them are reduced by the length of the smallest stick.

Suppose we have six sticks of the following lengths:
5 4 4 2 2 8

Then, in one cut operation we make a cut of length 2 from each of the six sticks. For the next cut operation four sticks are left (of non-zero length), whose lengths are the following: 
3 2 2 6

The above step is repeated until no sticks are left.

Given the length of NN sticks, print the number of sticks that are left before each subsequent cut operations.

Note: For each cut operation, you have to recalcuate the length of smallest sticks (excluding zero-length sticks).

Input Format 
The first line contains a single integer NN. 
The next line contains NN integers: a0, a1,...aN-1 separated by space, where ai represents the length of ith stick.

Output Format 
For each operation, print the number of sticks that are cut, on separate lines.

Constraints 
1 ≤ N ≤ 1000 
1 ≤ ai ≤ 1000

Sample Input #00

6
5 4 4 2 2 8
Sample Output #00

6
4
2
1
Sample Input #01

8
1 2 3 4 3 3 2 1
Sample Output #01

8
6
4
1