Little Bob loves chocolate, and he goes to a store with $N$N in his pocket. The price of each chocolate is $C$C. The store offers a discount: for every MM wrappers he gives to the store, he gets one chocolate for free. How many chocolates does Bob get to eat?

Input Format: 
The first line contains the number of test cases, TT. 
TT lines follow, each of which contains three integers, NN, CC, and MM.

Output Format: 
Print the total number of chocolates Bob eats.

Constraints: 
1≤T≤10001≤T≤1000 
2≤N≤1052≤N≤105 
1≤C≤N1≤C≤N 
2≤M≤N2≤M≤N

Sample input

3
10 2 5
12 4 4
6 2 2
Sample Output

6
3
5